<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2018-04-22T09:46:00+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Early stage affiliate marketing</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/early-stage-affiliate-marketing/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/early-stage-affiliate-marketing/</id>
    <published>2018-04-22T09:46:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2018-08-28T17:18:41+02:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey all welcome to another episode of Seeking Traction so after the launch someone posted about MightyScout in an
Italian Facebook group: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep3-fbgroup.png" alt="Facebook group post of MightyScout" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and that led to a lot of different Italian users signing up. And one person who&amp;rsquo;s also Italian, ended up messaging us &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep3-intro-email.png" alt="Intro email reaching out to help" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;turns out that he has built courses for growing your Instagram following and has a community specifically around Instagram along with an email list. So we started talking about doing things like an affiliate marketing type setup and having him talk to these Italian specific leads in Italian and we can use like a custom email there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep3-affiliate-marketing.png" alt="Affiliate marketing checklist, existing leads, referral code, custom email, demo/education" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re gonna need to create a referral link so that anything that he posts online we can credit to him and then also we&amp;rsquo;re gonna need to do a demo and education on the nuances of the platform so that he&amp;rsquo;s talking about making like content online that talks about the product and how to use it. But we&amp;rsquo;ll see how it goes and if you have any questions be sure to leave them in the comments and I&amp;rsquo;ll see you next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Building a habit. Facebook &amp; Email Ads</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/building-a-habit-facebook-email-ads/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/building-a-habit-facebook-email-ads/</id>
    <published>2018-04-20T09:46:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2018-08-30T15:21:42+02:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;All right we&amp;rsquo;re about two weeks into the product hunt launch so we have a bunch of new users that are on the site using it regularly. The thing we&amp;rsquo;re trying to do, and we should have done this earlier, but we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make sure MightyScout is top of mind with these new users. So when someone uses a brand new tool or new website they can very easily forget about it the same day or within just a few hours because it&amp;rsquo;s not a habit yet. So that&amp;rsquo;s why there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of activation emails and different emails that people send which we&amp;rsquo;ve also been doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video autoplay loop muted playsinline class="js-looping-video"&gt;&lt;source src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep2-emails.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we want to try to get at least like three emails and within the first seven days and then getting some ads in as well would be great and the ads are mostly just retargeting so that when people are browsing you know their Twitter feeds and Facebook feeds they still have MightyScout top-of-mind so they&amp;rsquo;re aware that our tool exists to hopefully get them to use the site a few more times to where it becomes more of a habit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video autoplay loop muted playsinline class="js-looping-video"&gt;&lt;source src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep2-ads.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s really cool with like social networking sites and things like that is you can have reactivation emails when people like your stuff or comments you have these natural behaviors where you want to come back and use the product with sass it more feels like you need to really get attached to the workflow so when someone thinks hey I need to find an influencer or I need to
understand their stats they think MightyScout so we are trying to really own that mind space but it&amp;rsquo;s something that is difficult to do very early on since the product is new.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>MightyScout ProductHunt Launch</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/mightyscout-producthunt-launch/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/mightyscout-producthunt-launch/</id>
    <published>2018-04-16T09:46:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2018-08-30T15:21:08+02:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;All right here&amp;rsquo;s the first episode of Seeking Traction, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna go over MightyScout a product I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for a little bit more than a year and our launch on the Product Hunt about a week ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/mightyscout-lookup-home.png" alt="MightyScout Lookup Homepage" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this time we were just getting all the images together and just trying to get this thing out the door there are just so many things going on with the last-minute changes and fixes the website but yeah here we go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video autoplay loop muted playsinline class="js-looping-video"&gt;&lt;source src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/launch-moment-short.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now the site&amp;rsquo;s live and I mean it&amp;rsquo;s huge relief but we start running into issues with I didn&amp;rsquo;t know that there is
supposed to be a description, there&amp;rsquo;s all sorts of stuff on the right side that needs to be filled out I wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware that we needed any of this stuff&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep1-ph-page-missing.png" alt="image of needed description, social links, etc" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and then the biggest thing is the gif that we had prepared is just too big so you could see how I was like blurry even as people are starting off a product &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video autoplay loop muted playsinline class="js-looping-video"&gt;&lt;source src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep1-blurry-gif.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;so I&amp;rsquo;m just scrambling trying to find a way to display this thing in a much better format so I&amp;rsquo;m like using [Kippur] [cisors] and all sorts of different things and just like really trying to figure out how can we minimize the size to show it in its best light and ultimately I&amp;rsquo;m just playing around with all these image settings and I end up putting up an image for the time being and then I had to reshoot an entire little clip that was small enough to be around like three megabytes so that they can load fairly decently on the site but yeah huge relief&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id="results"&gt;Results&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/seeking-traction/ep1-results.png" alt="img of results, 3,377 visitors, 9,285 searches, 270 new users, $155 in sales, 2 solid leads" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
